Guide to the North Carolina State University, Athletics, Football Audiovisual Materials
North Carolina State University, Athletics, Football Audiovisual Materials
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (2 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 19 Oct. 1985 (Carton 103)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (3 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 19 Oct. 1985 (Carton 51)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (4 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 19 Oct. 1985 (Carton 103)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (5 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 19 Oct. 1985 (Carton 52)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (6 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 19 Oct. 1985 (Carton 103)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (7 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 19 Oct. 1985 (Carton 52)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (8 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 19 Oct. 1985 (Carton 103)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (9 of 10) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 19 Oct. 1985 (Carton 52)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (10 of 10) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 19 Oct. 1985 (Carton 103)
- NC State vs. Virginia (1 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 9 Nov. 1985 (Carton 52)
- NC State vs. Virginia (2 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 9 Nov. 1985 (Carton 103)
- NC State vs. Virginia (3 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 9 Nov. 1985 (Carton 52)
- NC State vs. Virginia (4 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 9 Nov. 1985 (Carton 103)
- NC State vs. Virginia (5 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 9 Nov. 1985 (Carton 52)
- NC State vs. Virginia (6 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 9 Nov. 1985 (Carton 52)
- NC State vs. Virginia (7 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 9 Nov. 1985 (Carton 103)
- NC State vs. Virginia (8 of 8) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 9 Nov. 1985 (Carton 52)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (1 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 21 Sept. 1985 (Carton 52)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (2 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 21 Sept. 1985 (Carton 103)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (3 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 21 Sept. 1985 (Carton 52)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (4 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 21 Sept. 1985 (Carton 103)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (5 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 21 Sept. 1985 (Carton 52)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (6 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 21 Sept. 1985 (Carton 52)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (7 of 8) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 21 Sept. 1985 (Carton 52)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (8 of 8) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 21 Sept. 1985 (Carton 103)
- NC State vs. Clemson (1 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 25 Oct. 1986 (Carton 52)
- NC State vs. Clemson (2 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 25 Oct. 1986 (Carton 103)
- NC State vs. Clemson (3 of 9) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 25 Oct. 1986 (Carton 52)
- NC State vs. Clemson (4 of 9) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 25 Oct. 1986 (Carton 103)
- NC State vs. Clemson (5 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 25 Oct. 1986 (Carton 52)
- NC State vs. Clemson (6 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 25 Oct. 1986 (Carton 103)
- NC State vs. Clemson (7 of 9) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 25 Oct. 1986 (Carton 52)
- NC State vs. Clemson (8 of 9) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 25 Oct. 1986 (Carton 103)
- NC State vs. Clemson (9 of 9) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 25 Oct. 1986 (Carton 52)
- NC State vs. Duke (1 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 15 Nov. 1986 (Carton 103)
- NC State vs. Duke (2 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 15 Nov. 1986 (Carton 103)
- NC State vs. Duke (3 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 15 Nov. 1986 (Carton 52)
- NC State vs. Duke (4 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 15 Nov. 1986 (Carton 103)
- NC State vs. Duke (5 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 15 Nov. 1986 (Carton 52)
- NC State vs. Duke (6 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 15 Nov. 1986 (Carton 103)
- NC State vs. Duke (7 of 8) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 15 Nov. 1986 (Carton 52)
- NC State vs. Duke (8 of 8) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 15 Nov. 1986 (Carton 103)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (1 of 7) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 6 Sept. 1986 (Carton 52)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (2 of 7) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 6 Sept. 1986 (Carton 52)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (3 of 7) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 6 Sept. 1986 (Carton 52)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (4 of 7) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 6 Sept. 1986 (Carton 103)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (5 of 7) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 6 Sept. 1986 (Carton 53)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (6 of 7) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 6 Sept. 1986 (Carton 104)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (7 of 7) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 6 Sept. 1986 (Carton 53)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (1 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense] (copy 1), 11 Oct. 1986 (Carton 53)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (2 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense] (copy 2), 11 Oct. 1986 (Carton 53)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (3 of 9) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 11 Oct. 1986 (Carton 104)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (4 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 11 Oct. 1986 (Carton 53)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (5 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 11 Oct. 1986 (Carton 104)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (6 of 9) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 11 Oct. 1986 (Carton 53)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (7 of 9) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 11 Oct. 1986 (Carton 104)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (8 of 9) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 11 Oct. 1986 (Carton 53)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (9 of 9) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 11 Oct. 1986 (Carton 104)
- NC State vs. Maryland (1 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 27 Sept. 1986 (Carton 104)
- NC State vs. Maryland (2 of 9) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 27 Sept. 1986 (Carton 104)
- NC State vs. Maryland (3 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 27 Sept. 1986 (Carton 53)
- NC State vs. Maryland (4 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 27 Sept. 1986 (Carton 104)
- NC State vs. Maryland (5 of 9) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 27 Sept. 1986 (Carton 53)
- NC State vs. Maryland (6 of 9) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense, Print #1], 27 Sept. 1986 (Carton 104)
- NC State vs. Maryland (7 of 9) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense, Print #2], 27 Sept. 1986 (Carton 104)
- NC State vs. Maryland (8 of 9) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 27 Sept. 1986 (Carton 53)
- NC State vs. Maryland (9 of 9) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 27 Sept. 1986 (Carton 104)
- NC State vs. Pittsburgh (1 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 13 Sept. 1986 (Carton 104)
- NC State vs. Pittsburgh (2 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 13 Sept. 1986 (Carton 104)
- NC State vs. Pittsburgh (3 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 13 Sept. 1986 (Carton 53)
- NC State vs. Pittsburgh (4 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 13 Sept. 1986 (Carton 104)
- NC State vs. Pittsburgh (5 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 13 Sept. 1986 (Carton 53)
- NC State vs. Pittsburgh (6 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 13 Sept. 1986 (Carton 104)
- NC State vs. Pittsburgh (7 of 8) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 13 Sept. 1986 (Carton 53)
- NC State vs. Pittsburgh (8 of 8) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 13 Sept. 1986 (Carton 104)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (1 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 1 Nov. 1986 (Carton 53)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (2 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 1 Nov. 1986 (Carton 104)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (3 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 1 Nov. 1986 (Carton 53)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (4 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 1 Nov. 1986 (Carton 104)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (5 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 1 Nov. 1986 (Carton 53)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (6 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 1 Nov. 1986 (Carton 104)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (7 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 1 Nov. 1986 (Carton 53)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (8 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 1 Nov. 1986 (Carton 104)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (9 of 10) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 1 Nov. 1986 (Carton 53)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (10 of 10) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 1 Nov. 1986 (Carton 104)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (1 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 18 Oct. 1986 (Carton 104)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (2 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 18 Oct. 1986 (Carton 104)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (3 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 18 Oct. 1986 (Carton 53)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (4 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 18 Oct. 1986 (Carton 104)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (5 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 18 Oct. 1986 (Carton 53)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (6 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 18 Oct. 1986 (Carton 105)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (7 of 8) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 18 Oct. 1986 (Carton 53)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (8 of 8) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 18 Oct. 1986 (Carton 105)
- NC State vs. Virginia (1 of 7) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 8 Nov. 1986 (Carton 105)
- NC State vs. Virginia (2 of 7) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 8 Nov. 1986 (Carton 105)
- NC State vs. Virginia (3 of 7) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 8 Nov. 1986 (Carton 53)
- NC State vs. Virginia (4 of 7) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 8 Nov. 1986 (Carton 105)
- NC State vs. Virginia (5 of 7) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 8 Nov. 1986 (Carton 53)
- NC State vs. Virginia (6 of 7) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 8 Nov. 1986 (Carton 105)
- NC State vs. Virginia (7 of 7) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 8 Nov. 1986 (Carton 105)
- NC State vs. Virginia Tech (Peach Bowl) (1 of 6) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 31 Dec. 1986 (Carton 53)
- NC State vs. Virginia Tech (Peach Bowl) (2 of 6) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 31 Dec. 1986 (Carton 54)
- NC State vs. Virginia Tech (Peach Bowl) (3 of 6) [labeled on canister as Defense #1], 31 Dec. 1986 (Carton 54)
- NC State vs. Virginia Tech (Peach Bowl) (4 of 6) [labeled on canister as Defense #2], 31 Dec. 1986 (Carton 54)
- NC State vs. Virginia Tech (Peach Bowl) (5 of 6) [labeled on canister as Defense #3], 31 Dec. 1986 (Carton 54)
- NC State vs. Virginia Tech (Peach Bowl) (6 of 6) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 31 Dec. 1986 (Carton 54)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (1 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 20 Sept. 1986 (Carton 105)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (2 of 9) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 20 Sept. 1986 (Carton 105)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (3 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 20 Sept. 1986 (Carton 54)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (4 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 20 Sept. 1986 (Carton 105)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (5 of 9) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 20 Sept. 1986 (Carton 105)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (6 of 9) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 20 Sept. 1986 (Carton 105)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (7 of 9) [labeled on canister as Reel #1], 20 Sept. 1986 (Carton 105)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (8 of 9) [labeled on canister as Reel #2], 20 Sept. 1986 (Carton 105)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (9 of 9) [labeled on canister as Reel #3], 20 Sept. 1986 (Carton 105)
- NC State vs. Western Carolina University (1 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 22 Nov. 1986 (Carton 54)
- NC State vs. Western Carolina University (2 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 22 Nov. 1986 (Carton 105)
- NC State vs. Western Carolina University (3 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 22 Nov. 1986 (Carton 54)
- NC State vs. Western Carolina University (4 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 22 Nov. 1986 (Carton 105)
- NC State vs. Western Carolina University (5 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 22 Nov. 1986 (Carton 54)
- NC State vs. Western Carolina University (6 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 22 Nov. 1986 (Carton 105)
- NC State vs. Western Carolina University (7 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 22 Nov. 1986 (Carton 54)
- NC State vs. Western Carolina University (8 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 22 Nov. 1986 (Carton 105)
- NC State vs. Western Carolina University (9 of 10) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 22 Nov. 1986 (Carton 54)
- NC State vs. Western Carolina University (10 of 10) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 22 Nov. 1986 (Carton 105)
- Highlights [on cassette w/footage from 1972 & 1978], 1986 (Carton 36)
- NC State vs. Clemson (1 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 24 Oct. 1987 (Carton 54)
- NC State vs. Clemson (2 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 24 Oct. 1987 (Carton 54)
- NC State vs. Clemson (3 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense, Print #1], 24 Oct. 1987 (Carton 105)
- NC State vs. Clemson (4 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense, Print #2], 24 Oct. 1987 (Carton 105)
- NC State vs. Clemson (5 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 24 Oct. 1987 (Carton 54)
- NC State vs. Clemson (6 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 24 Oct. 1987 (Carton 54)
- NC State vs. Clemson (7 of 8) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 24 Oct. 1987 (Carton 54)
- NC State vs. Clemson (8 of 8) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 24 Oct. 1987 (Carton 105)
- NC State vs. Duke (1 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 14 Nov. 1987 (Carton 54)
- NC State vs. Duke (2 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 14 Nov. 1987 (Carton 105)
- NC State vs. Duke (3 of 9) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 14 Nov. 1987 (Carton 54)
- NC State vs. Duke (4 of 9) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 14 Nov. 1987 (Carton 106)
- NC State vs. Duke (5 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 14 Nov. 1987 (Carton 54)
- NC State vs. Duke (6 of 9) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 14 Nov. 1987 (Carton 106)
- NC State vs. Duke (7 of 9) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 14 Nov. 1987 (Carton 54)
- NC State vs. Duke (8 of 9) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 14 Nov. 1987 (Carton 54)
- NC State vs. Duke (9 of 9) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 14 Nov. 1987 (Carton 106)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (1 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 5 Sept. 1987 (Carton 54)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (2 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 5 Sept. 1987 (Carton 106)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (3 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 5 Sept. 1987 (Carton 55)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (4 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 5 Sept. 1987 (Carton 106)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (5 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 5 Sept. 1987 (Carton 55)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (6 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 5 Sept. 1987 (Carton 55)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (7 of 8) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 5 Sept. 1987 (Carton 55)
- NC State vs. East Carolina University (8 of 8) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 5 Sept. 1987 (Carton 106)
- NC State vs. East Tennessee State University (1 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 7 Nov. 1987 (Carton 55)
- NC State vs. East Tennessee State University (2 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 7 Nov. 1987 (Carton 106)
- NC State vs. East Tennessee State University (3 of 5) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 7 Nov. 1987 (Carton 55)
- NC State vs. East Tennessee State University (4 of 5) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 7 Nov. 1987 (Carton 106)
- NC State vs. East Tennessee State University (5 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 7 Nov. 1987 (Carton 55)
- NC State vs. East Tennessee State University (6 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 7 Nov. 1987 (Carton 55)
- NC State vs. East Tennessee State University (7 of 8) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 7 Nov. 1987 (Carton 55)
- NC State vs. East Tennessee State University (8 of 8) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 7 Nov. 1987 (Carton 106)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (1 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 3 Oct. 1987 (Carton 55)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (2 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 3 Oct. 1987 (Carton 106)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (3 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 3 Oct. 1987 (Carton 55)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (4 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 3 Oct. 1987 (Carton 106)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (5 of 8) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 3 Oct. 1987 (Carton 55)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (6 of 8) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 3 Oct. 1987 (Carton 55)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (7 of 8) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 3 Oct. 1987 (Carton 55)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (8 of 8) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 3 Oct. 1987 (Carton 106)
- NC State vs. Maryland (1 of 11) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 26 Sept. 1987 (Carton 55)
- NC State vs. Maryland (2 of 11) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense, 1st Quarter], 26 Sept. 1987 (Carton 106)
- NC State vs. Maryland (3 of 11) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense, 2nd Quarter], 26 Sept. 1987 (Carton 106)
- NC State vs. Maryland (4 of 11) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 26 Sept. 1987 (Carton 55)
- NC State vs. Maryland (5 of 11) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 26 Sept. 1987 (Carton 106)
- NC State vs. Maryland (6 of 11) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 26 Sept. 1987 (Carton 55)
- NC State vs. Maryland (7 of 11) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 26 Sept. 1987 (Carton 106)
- NC State vs. Maryland (8 of 11) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 26 Sept. 1987 (Carton 55)
- NC State vs. Maryland (9 of 11) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 26 Sept. 1987 (Carton 106)
- NC State vs. Maryland (10 of 11) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 26 Sept. 1987 (Carton 55)
- NC State vs. Maryland (11 of 11) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 26 Sept. 1987 (Carton 106)
- NC State vs. Pittsburgh (1 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 12 Sept. 1987 (Carton 55)
- NC State vs. Pittsburgh (2 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 12 Sept. 1987 (Carton 106)
- NC State vs. Pittsburgh (3 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 12 Sept. 1987 (Carton 55)
- NC State vs. Pittsburgh (4 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 12 Sept. 1987 (Carton 106)
- NC State vs. Pittsburgh (5 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 12 Sept. 1987 (Carton 55)
- NC State vs. Pittsburgh (6 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 12 Sept. 1987 (Carton 106)
- NC State vs. Pittsburgh (7 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 12 Sept. 1987 (Carton 55)
- NC State vs. Pittsburgh (8 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 12 Sept. 1987 (Carton 106)
- NC State vs. Pittsburgh (9 of 10) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 12 Sept. 1987 (Carton 55)
- NC State vs. Pittsburgh (10 of 10) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 12 Sept. 1987 (Carton 106)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (1 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 31 Oct. 1987 (Carton 56)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (2 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 31 Oct. 1987 (Carton 106)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (3 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 31 Oct. 1987 (Carton 56)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (4 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 31 Oct. 1987 (Carton 107)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (5 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 31 Oct. 1987 (Carton 56)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (6 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 31 Oct. 1987 (Carton 107)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (7 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 31 Oct. 1987 (Carton 56)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (8 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 31 Oct. 1987 (Carton 107)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (9 of 10) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 31 Oct. 1987 (Carton 56)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (10 of 10) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 31 Oct. 1987 (Carton 107)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (1 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 17 Oct. 1987 (Carton 56)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (2 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 17 Oct. 1987 (Carton 107)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (3 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 17 Oct. 1987 (Carton 56)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (4 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 17 Oct. 1987 (Carton 107)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (5 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 17 Oct. 1987 (Carton 56)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (6 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 17 Oct. 1987 (Carton 107)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (7 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 17 Oct. 1987 (Carton 56)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (8 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 17 Oct. 1987 (Carton 107)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (9 of 10) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 17 Oct. 1987 (Carton 56)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (10 of 10) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 17 Oct. 1987 (Carton 107)
- NC State vs. Virginia (1 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 21 Nov. 1987 (Carton 56)
- NC State vs. Virginia (2 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 21 Nov. 1987 (Carton 107)
- NC State vs. Virginia (3 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 21 Nov. 1987 (Carton 56)
- NC State vs. Virginia (4 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 21 Nov. 1987 (Carton 107)
- NC State vs. Virginia (5 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 21 Nov. 1987 (Carton 56)
- NC State vs. Virginia (6 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 21 Nov. 1987 (Carton 107)
- NC State vs. Virginia (7 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 21 Nov. 1987 (Carton 56)
- NC State vs. Virginia (8 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 21 Nov. 1987 (Carton 107)
- NC State vs. Virginia (9 of 10) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 21 Nov. 1987 (Carton 56)
- NC State vs. Virginia (10 of 10) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 21 Nov. 1987 (Carton 107)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (1 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 19 Sept. 1987 (Carton 56)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (2 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 19 Sept. 1987 (Carton 107)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (3 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 19 Sept. 1987 (Carton 56)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (4 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 19 Sept. 1987 (Carton 107)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (5 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 19 Sept. 1987 (Carton 56)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (6 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 19 Sept. 1987 (Carton 107)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (7 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 19 Sept. 1987 (Carton 56)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (8 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 19 Sept. 1987 (Carton 107)